Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Thomas Sutton Papers, 1965-1975 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Restricted Materials, 1966-1968, (1 box)
  - Central and South American Offices Files Series, 1966-1968 and undated
    - Argentina, 1967-1968
      - Salaries and profit sharing, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
    - Brazil, 1966-1968 and undated
      - Cavalcanti, Carlos, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Kfuri, Joe, 1967 (Box 11)
      - Personnel, 1968 and undated (Box 11)
      - Salaries and profit sharing, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Transfers of JWT employees, 1966, 1968
        - Eaves, Elliott, 1968 (Box 11)
        - Gibson, Chuck, 1968 (Box 11)
        - Raibourn, Gerald, 1966, 1968 (Box 11)
        - Wallace, Robert, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Chile, 1968
      - Personnel, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Salaries and profit sharing, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Mexico, 1967-1968
      - Personnel, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Salary increases, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
    - Peru, 1967-1968
      - Personnel, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
      - Salaries and profit sharing, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
- Removed Items, (1 box)
  Restriction on access: Original is closed to patrons. A Use Copy is available to patrons.
  - Annual Marketing Plans and Reports Series, 1968
    - Pacific Area, JWT Australia
      - Annual report (original, Use Copy in files, box 10), 1968 (Box 11)